Gonzalo Hernández Full Stack Developer

Madrid, Spain

4 658 836 097

■ gonzalohernandez@icloud.com

in linkedin.com/in/ghgarcia/

github.com/hernandezgonzalo

gonzalohernandez.es



Profile

Hi! I'm Gonzalo, graduated in Advertising and Public Relations and a Higher Technician in Computer Systems Management. I have more than ten years of experience in Digital Marketing. I consider myself a versatile and responsible person, who possesses self-discipline, is deadline orientated and has the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively.

Professional Experience

Making Golf

01/2019 - present

Head of the Digital Marketing Department

Madrid, Spain

Responsible for the visual identity and digital communication of the group companies

10/2012 - 12/2018

Front-end Web Developer and Digital Marketing Specialist

Madrid, Spain

Web development (JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, WordPress)

• SEO, SEM and Web Analytics, Social Media (CM) and Social Ads, Email Marketing

08/2010 - 10/2012

Graphic Web Designer

Web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flash)

Illustration and layout, photography and video editing

04/2006 - 11/2008 Madrid, Spain

Madrid, Spain

COMPOSAN Industrial y Tecnología, Information Technology Technician

Helpdesk support and network management

Skills

JavaScript, React, Redux, React Native, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS, SASS, jQuery, Handlebars, AJAX, WebSockets, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Git, TypeScript, TDD

Projects

04/2020 - 04/2020	COVID-19 Pandemic Statistics, Application to keep track of coronavirus cases
	Final project to be made during the Ironhack Web Development Bootcamp. A full-stack web application developed with React, Node.js, Express and MongoDB.

Education

10/2019 - 04/2020	Ironhack, Web Development Bootcamp JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3, SASS and TDD principles
2013 - 2018	Universidad Rey Juan Carlos, Advertising and Public Relations
2004 - 2006	Instituto Virgen de la Paz, Computer Systems Management

Soft skills

Versatility, responsibility, verbal communication, open-mindedness, analysis, organization and design.

Languages

Spanish	English	

Interests

I like to attend music concerts, play the guitar, play sports, technology and astronomy.